

Rafał Bierzanek

software tester

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Over the past few years, I have moved to the real estate industry, where I went through all possible specialties: property management, real estate appraisal and sales brokerage I made the decision to rearrange 2 years ago and during this period I have had many trainings, webinars, online courses and participated in projects related to training in the IT industry. Analyzing my hard knowledge in the field of IT and knowing my interpersonal communication skills and analytical skills confirmed in the real estate industry, I believe that the choice of the way to a manual tester and in the near future an automation tester is the optimal goal for me.

WORK EXPERIENCES

12.2021

practice "manual testing"

testerzy.pl

02.2020

final training project with UX Design

"Redesign procesu dodawania ogłoszenia w portalu Morizon.pl". https://uxfol.io/p/homefac /0468ba4c

12.2019

final training project with Fronted Developer "weather application"

https://github.com/RafalBie/weather-application

11.2018 - 12.2019

web design by Wordpress

freelancing

03.2014 — present

CEO Home Factor

real estate broker, short-term rental management

02.2013 - 01.2014

real estate appraiser

With Money

01.2012 - 12.2012

real estate broker

Krupa Nieruchomości

EDUCATION

10.2022 - 10.2022

Training "ISTQB Foundation Level" testerzy .pl

11.2021

Training "Profession Tester" testerzy .pl

02.2020

UX Designer Future Collars

12.2019

Fronted Developer Future Collars

11.2018

Wordpress with SEO positioning GO WORK

PERSONAL DETAILS

Email:

rafbierzanek@gmail.com

Phone number:

+48 501782755

Address:

Warsaw

SITES AND SOCIAL LINKS

GitHub

HARD SKILLS

Knowledge of ISTQB FL

Create scenarios and test cases

 $basic\ knowledge\ HTML/CSS/JAVA$

SCRIPT/REACT

UX DESIGN
WORDPRESS

Development tools: VS Code

Version control system: GIT

Jira

Postman API

MS Office

LANGUAGES

English - B2

Spanish - A2

Russian - A1

SGH, Warsaw

INTERESTS

Street photography bicycle trips

SOFT SKILLS

Effective communication ability

Developed analytical thinking skills

Cooperation

Emotional Intelligence

Multitasking

Trainable

Critical thinking

I hereby consent to my personal data being processed for the purpose of considering my application for the vacancy.